seshamo.com 2009-04-14

# Privacy - Seshamo

This policy has been developed because we want you to feel confident about the privacy and security of your personal information entered on our site. We follow strict security procedures in the storage and disclosure of your information as required by law.   
All personal information will be held in strictest confidence and used only for the purposes for providing you the service requested with certain caveats as described below.

## General

At the Altura Labs s.r.l. Network we respect the privacy of all our users, and follow a strict privacy policy. This policy ensures total confidentiality concerning any personal details or information submitted via the network, so customers can rest assured their privacy will be respected.

## Standard User Data

Upon logging on to the network , our servers collect certain elements of standard information. This data includes but is not limited to: the website from which you came, the amount of time you spend on various areas of the network or any related sites, your browser software (ie Internet Explorer, Mozilla Firefox), any accessed information from the network and any downloaded pages. This type of data collection is common throughout most websites, and in no way impinges on your privacy. It is essential to note that the data collected does not identify you, and provides no information as to personal details. No data will be disclosed in such a way that it identifies you personally, unless otherwise stated. Before reading any content or using any services found in this network, you are confirming you understand the nature of this data collection, and have read and understood our privacy policy. The Altura Labs s.r.l. Network sites not gather, retain and/or disclose any standard data other than in collective user data forms.

## Personal User Data

The only occasion on which the Altura Labs s.r.l. Network may receive personally identifiable information about you is if you, the user, knowingly and willingly provide us with the information via email. This information is voluntarily submitted at your discretion, and is optional and normally required so as to allow us to reply to your email and correspondence. The network will never share with advertisers or other third parties the aggregate results of the data it receives except as indicated below, or except when we inform you in advance and give you the opportunity to opt out. We may share personal information with:

  1. Service providers, such as credit-card payment processors, performing services on our behalf;
  2. Other businesses with which we partner or which we carefully select to offer you products, services, and promotions through our website or offline; and
  3. Other third parties in limited circumstances, such as complying with legal requirements, preventing fraud, and protecting the safety of our users.

## Cookies

A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.   
Your IP address is a series of numbers which identify a computer on the internet. We use IP addresses to help diagnose possible service interruptions and administer our service and website.   
Some parts of the network use cookies to provide better services and information for users. A cookie is a file transferred by a website to a user’s personal computer in order to keep records. Many websites, including the Altura Network, employ cookies to enhance services and content. Cookies are stored not on our servers, but on your personal computer these files are small, and do not identify you personally in any way.

## Disabling Cookies

Cookies can be disabled in your browsers settings.   
For detailed instructions on how to disable cookies using (amongst others) Mozilla, Netscape Navigator and Internet Explorer, visit:   
For more information, see <http://support.microsoft.com/kb/260971>, <http://kb.mozillazine.org/Network.cookie.cookieBehavior>.

## Third party security

We cannot be responsible for the privacy policies and practices of other websites, even if you access them using links from our website and recommend that you check the policy of each site you visit.

## Children

Users of all ages are welcome to our content and services. If you are under the age of thirteen (13), we do, however, specifically request that you have the permission of parents or legal guardians to view any content within the network, as we cannot and will not be held responsible for any information received or disclosed by our users.   
Be aware  
Please be aware that communications over the Internet, such as emails/webmails, are not secure unless they have been encrypted. Your communications may route through a number of countries before being delivered – this is the nature of the World Wide Web/Internet. We cannot accept responsibility for any unauthorised access or loss of personal information that is beyond our control.

Altura Labs s.r.l.
